[
  {
    "name": "HTML5",
    "front": "11",
    "back":"11"
  },
  {
    "name": "CSS3",
    "front": "22",
    "back":"22"
  },
  {
    "name": "Scss",
    "front": "99",
    "back":"11091"
  },
  {
    "name": "JavaScript",
    "front": "ES5/ES6",
    "back":"33"
  },
  {
    "name": "TypeScript",
    "front": "1818",
    "back":"11181"
  },
  {
    "name": "jQuery",
    "front": "44",
    "back":"44"
  },
  {
    "name": "Bootstrap4",
    "front": "55",
    "back":"55"
  },
  {
    "name": "React",
    "front": "Redux/React-redux/Ajax/Route4",
    "back":"66"
  },
  {
    "name": "Angular",
    "front": "RxJS/NgRx",
    "back":"11201"
  },
  {
    "name": "Ionic5",
    "front": "2020",
    "back":"11201"
  },
  {
    "name": "Ant Mobile",
    "front": "2020",
    "back":"11201"
  },
  {
    "name": "NodeJS",
    "front": "10",
    "back":"11011"
  },
  {
    "name": "SQL",
    "front": "MySQL/MariaDB/SQLite",
    "back":"11311"
  },
  {
    "name": "NoSQL",
    "front": "MongoDB",
    "back":"11141"
  },
  {
    "name": "Webpack4",
    "front": "11",
    "back":"111"
  },
  {
    "name": "Electron",
    "front": "2020",
    "back":"11201"
  },
  {
    "name": "Git",
    "front": "1212",
    "back":"11121"
  },
  {
    "name": "PHP",
    "front": "1515",
    "back":"11151"
  },
  {
    "name": "Laravel",
    "front": "2020",
    "back":"11201"
  },
  {
    "name": "Linux",
    "front": "Ubuntu/CentOS/Mint",
    "back":"11161"
  },
  {
    "name": "Server",
    "front": "Apache/Tomcat/Nginx",
    "back":"11201"
  },
  {
    "name": "Docker",
    "front": "aa",
    "back":"11201"
  },
  {
    "name": "WordPress",
    "front": "1717",
    "back":"11171"
  },
  {
    "name": "Drupal 8",
    "front": "2020",
    "back":"11201"
  },
  {
    "name": ".NET",
    "front": "1919",
    "back":"11191"
  },
  {
    "name": "Java",
    "front": "77",
    "back":"1071"
  },
  {
    "name": "Python",
    "front": "88",
    "back":"11081"
  },
  {
    "name": "Gatsby",
    "front": "77",
    "back":"1071"
  }
]